{
  "results": [
    {
      "question": "A numeric ranking of a task's importance and appropriateness for leveling is called ________.",
      "correct_answer": "task priorities",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "load balancing",
        "random selection",
        "task deadlines"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "A better approach to scheduling tasks is to use a deadline date rather than a(n) ________.",
      "correct_answer": "slack",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "priority",
        "connection",
        "delaying"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "When you link the tasks in a project schedule, you establish a(n) ________ between the tasks.",
      "correct_answer": "relationship",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "constraint",
        "deadline",
        "0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "________ is the process of delaying a resource's work on a task to resolve an overallocation.",
      "correct_answer": "leveling",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "start-to-start",
        "finish-no-earlier-than",
        "start-no-later-than"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Microsoft Project honors constraint dates over task relationships, even if this causes ________.",
      "correct_answer": "negative slack",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "load balancing",
        "random selection",
        "task deadlines"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Tasks with a priority of ________ are leveled first.",
      "correct_answer": "0",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1",
        "100",
        "500"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "When you enter a deadline date, Microsoft Project alerts you if the task's ________ moves beyond the deadline.",
      "correct_answer": "completion",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "slack",
        "priority",
        "connection"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "A(n) ________ is a value you enter for a task that indicates the latest date by which you want the task to be completed.",
      "correct_answer": "deadline date",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "constraint date",
        "resource",
        "baseline"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The default task priority value for all tasks is ________.",
      "correct_answer": "500",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "100"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Tasks with a priority of ________ are never delayed by leveling.",
      "correct_answer": "1000",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "500"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Microsoft Project uses __________ to determine which tasks can be delayed in order to resolve periods of resource overallocation.",
      "correct_answer": "task priorities",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "load balancing",
        "random selection",
        "task deadlines"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is the numeric ranking range for task priority?",
      "correct_answer": "1 to 100",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "0 to 100",
        "1 to 500",
        "0 to 1000"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Entering a deadline date has no effect on the scheduling of a summary or subtask, except when the task involves which of the following?",
      "correct_answer": "the critical path",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "slack",
        "priority",
        "relationships"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a semi\u2010flexible constraint?",
      "correct_answer": "start no later than",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "start no earlier than",
        "must start on",
        "finish no earlier than"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Depending on options you choose, resource leveling might __________.",
      "correct_answer": "all of the above",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "delay the start date of a specific resource's assignment",
        "delay the start date of an entire task",
        "split up the work on a task"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following must be done to remove a deadline from a task?",
      "correct_answer": "Clear the Deadline field on the Advanced tab of the Task Information dialog box.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Delete the deadline indicator from the bar chart portion of the Gantt chart.",
        "Slide the deadline indicator off of the active portion of the Gantt chart.",
        "Change the deadline date to 00/00/00."
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of task relationship?",
      "correct_answer": "start no earlier than finish",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "finish to start",
        "finish to finish",
        "start to start"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "A deadline date __________.",
      "correct_answer": "is a semi\u2010flexible constraint",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "is the due date of the project",
        "does not constrain a task",
        "is not indicated on the Gantt chart"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following allows the most flexibility in scheduling a task?",
      "correct_answer": "inflexible constraint",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "semi\u2010flexible constraint",
        "deadline date",
        "none of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "By default, Microsoft Project honors which of the following?",
      "correct_answer": "constraint dates over relationships",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "deadline dates over relationships",
        "relationships over constraint dates",
        "negative slack over relationships"
      ]
    }
  ],
  "setCount": 1
}